mysticboard.com 2013-09-23

# MysticBoard.com - Privacy Policy - Mystic Board

All products and services such as Mystic Board Forum, Mystic Scripts and Mystic Softwares provided by MysticBoard.com under brands "Mystic Board Forum", "Mystic Scripts" and "Mystic Softwares" for the purpose of this Privacy Policy will be collectively called "MysticBoard.com".

Each and every person has the right to privacy. And, we do respect the right to privacy that our customers and regular visitors have.

We only collect minimum personal information that is required in order to run the site. Here is the list of the probable usages of your personal information that you give us.

We need your e-mail address in order that you can be updated with whatever is new on Mystic Board. This address is also used when a communication with the customer is necessary. But it is never revealed to anyone else.

Some of your personal information is necessary for us to know since they help us to determine at our discretion in your eligibility to receive post-buy support.

Your personal information as provided by yourself may be used as a part of survey with an attempt to find what more is necessary for the further betterment of Mystic Board. But this will not be done without giving you prior notification.

The information about your date of birth, place, that you provide for getting different readings such as but not limited to Astrology reading, Psychic, Tarot, numerology reading, are essentially necessary for the calculation and interpretation. This information is not stored by Mystic Software or Mystic Scripts. However, if you choose to post the above mentioned data publicly on MysticBoard.com Forum or elsewhere on our site, we have no control over who has access to it because of the nature of online forums.

If you choose to post your data we have no control over how different website(s) including but not limited to the various search engines may or may not use the data or how the search engines index such data in their search results. Please contact the website(s) who have used / accessed your data directly.

We use Google, as a third party vendor to serve ads on all sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit sites on the Internet. ( https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557&sourceid=aso ) .

MysticBoard.com privacy policy does not apply to and has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices. Please see <http://www.google.com/privacy/faq.html> for more details and to contact Google.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any point of time and at the discretion of MysticBoard.com management.
